

SABRINA D TELIS

Graphic Designer/Customer Service

- https://sabrinadelilaarts.com
- 813-624-4884
- sabrinadelilaarts@gmail.com
- 1320 Pasadena Bloom Lane, Ruskin FL 33570

EDUCATION

Associate in Arts Hillsborough Community College

Graphic Design Certification Hillsborough Community College 2023

PTK Honors Society 4.0 GPA

EXPERTISE

- Graphic Design
- Illustration
- **Customer Service**
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign & Lightroom
- Figma

ROLES & AWARDS

- President of HCC Art Club 2023
- PTK All-Florida Academic Team
- 49th & 50th Annual HCC Student Juried Art Exhibition
- Art Ascent magazine Artists of Abstract | 2020 Aug edition

ABOUT ME

Accomplished freelance graphic designer with 5 years of experience. Published illustrations in books, magazines & marketing content. Many years of experience in customer service therefore skilled in a fast-paced environment while creating positive customer experience. Looking for a company that aligns with strong values and a passion for creativity. A team player and always willing to help others. Dedicated to learning new skills to implement and always seeking ways to expand expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Q 2019 - Present Sabrina Delila Arts I Apollo Beach, FL

Freelance Graphic Designer & Illustrator

Matching with clients in need of illustration or design. Illustrated the cover and chapter images for Heaven's Bell by Sherrie Barch available in Barnes & Noble & Amazon as well as their marketing images. Designing logos and branding guides for local companies. Creating personalized family & memorial portraits on my Etsy.

2015 - 2019

Laser Spine Institute | Tampa, FL

Report Intake Specialist & Customer Service Rep

Operating a multi-line phone system for patient service calls & training new hires. Charting patient notes and responding to chats and emails simultaneously. Created and implemented a Standard Operating Procedure manual for the customer service team. Contacted imaging facilities to obtain medical records for our patients via phone, email, and faxing requests. Data input into Salesforce.

2014 - 2015

The Disney Store | Brandon, FL

Cast Member

Created a magical and fun environment for guests. Cash register experience and incoming calls. Stocking shelves and unpacking new products. Participated in Disney's VoluntEARS.

REFERENCES

Emily Troche Laser Spine Institute Sherrie Barch Heaven's Bell Author Omar Richardson O Richardson Design

Phone: (813) 957-0746

Phone: (815) 494-6496 Email: emilytroche12@yahoo.com Email: sherbarch@gmail.com

Phone: (912)-604-2070 Email: orichardson3@hccfl.edu